Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series I: Washington Square Dean's Files, 168422
  - Subseries B: Subject Files, 168849
    - Purchasing, 1969-1977; 168880 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Room Reservations, 1967-1976; 168879 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Space, 1959-1963; 168878 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225988 0
    - Statistical Tabulations, 1960; 168877 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1957; 169157 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1958-1967; 168876 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1968; 168875 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1969; 168874 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1970; 168873 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1971; 168872 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1972; 168871 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1973; 168870 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1974; 168869 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1975; 168868 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1976; 168867 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1977; 168866 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Sunrise Semester: Budget, 1969-1972; 168865 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Sunrise Semester: Budget, 1973-1979; 168864 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Sunrise Semester: California State College, Sonoma, 1974-1975; 168863 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Sunrise Semester: College Credit for High School Students, 1971; 168862 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Sunrise Semester: Course Lists and Distribution List, 1957-1978; 168861 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: American Telephone and Telegraph, 1972; 168860 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: Danforth Foundation, 1972; 168859 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: Pragma Corporation, 1977; 168858 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: John D. Rockefeller, 3rd Fund, 1974; 168857 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: Shop-Rite, 1974-1975; 168856 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Sunrise Semester: Fund Raising: Sperry and Hutchinson Company, 1972-1975; 168855 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Sunrise Semester: Proposed Courses, 1974-1976; 168854 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225989 8
    - Sunrise Semester: Proposed Courses, 1977-1978; 168853 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Sunrise Semester: Tapes for Re-use, 1973-1974; 168852 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Travel Expenses, 1974-1976; 168851 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 21 Club, 1975; 168850 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Educational Policy Committee, 168776
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1965-1966; 185335 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1970-1971; 185336 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: General, 1971-1972; 185337 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Achievement Tests, 1968; 185338 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Actions Completed (Hindle), 1966-1967; 185339 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Admissions Standards, 1958-1964; 168848 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225990 6
    - Educational Policy Committee: Advanced Standing, 1958-1963; 168847 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: American Civilization Concentration, 1968 December 12; 185340 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Announcements, Minutes, Reports, 1966; 185341 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Annual Report to the Dean, 1969; 185342 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Anthropology (Hindle), 1966; 185343 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Black Studies, 1969; 185344 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Brazil Junior Year Program, 1961; 168846 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Attendance, 1958-1968; 168845 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Scheduling, 1963-1965; 168844 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Class Size, 1957-1964; 168843 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Completed Business (Minor), 1966; 185345 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Coordinated Liberal Studies, Commission on, 1969-1978; 168842 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence, 1966; 185346 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence, 1969-1970; 185347 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Correspondence and Minutes, 1964-1965; 185348 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Courses Approved, 1971-1972; 168841 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Courses to be Approved, 1972; 168840 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Creative Arts, 1966-1967; 185349 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Curricular Innovation Fund, 1968-1969; 185350 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Curriculum Committee, Undergraduate, 1972-1973; 168839 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Debating, 1961-1962; 168838 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Departmental Planning, 1965; 168837 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Discipline Procedures, 1969; 185351 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Dramatic Literature Major, 1967; 168836 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: East Asian Studies, 1968; 168835 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Electives, 1965; 168834 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English Courses, 1960-1968; 168833 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English Major, 1963; 168832 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: English 1roficiency, 1959-1966; 168831 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Evening Program, 1959-1964; 168830 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Examinations, 1965; 168829 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Examinations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1964-1965; 168828 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225991 4
    - Educational Policy Committee: F Grade Substitution, 1962-1964; 168827 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Faculty Role, Definition of, 1968; 168826 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Foreign Language Requirements, 1953-1967; 168825 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Foreign Students, 1960-1965; 168824 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Four-Course Plan, 1967; 168823 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Four-Course Plan, 1969; 185352 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Freshman Orientation, 1957; 168822 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Gallatin Divison, 1962; 168821 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Geology, 1951-1962; 168820 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Geophysics, 1960; 168819 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Germany Study Program, 1965-1966; 168818 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Grading (Pass-Fail and Plus-Minus), 1964-1969; 185353 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Grading System, 1957-1968; 168817 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Courses, 1957-1968; 168816 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Record Exam, 1961; 168815 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Study in Psychology, 1968; 185354 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Graduate Survey, 1966; 185355 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hanging Business (Minor), 1965-1966; 185356 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hebrew, 1959-1965; 168814 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Honors, 1959-1966; 168813 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Hours, 1968; 185357 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Independent Study, 1957-1960; 168812 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Israel Summer Session, 1960; 168811 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Linguistics Major, 1964; 168810 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Major Selection, 1965; 168809 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mandate, 1951-1965; 168808 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mathematics Major, 1958-1965; 168807 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Membership, 1962-1963; 168806 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Metropolitan Leadership Program Evaluation, 1968 November 1; 185358 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Mid-Term Grades, 1968; 168805 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minor Requirements, 1957-1963; 168804 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1966-1967; 185359 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1966-1967; 185360 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1967-1968; 185361 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1968-1969; 185362 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1970-1971; 185363 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Minutes, 1971-1972; 185364 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Educational Policy Committee: N Grade, 1966; 168803 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Educational Policy Committee: New General Program, 1956; 168802 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Non-Liberal Arts Credit, 1963; 168801 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Philosophy, 1958-1961; 168800 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Physical Education, 1962-1965; 168799 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Physical Science, 1963; 168798 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225992 2
    - Educational Policy Committee: Planning, 1968-1969; 185365 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Portuguese-Brazilian major, 1958-1965; 168797 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Proficiency Examination, 1968; 168796 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Educational Policy Committee: R Course Requirement, 1961-1962; 168795 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reading Period, 1966-1968; 168794 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reading Week, 1968; 185366 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Recommendations on Faculty Involvement (Hindle), circa 1960s-1970s; 185367 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Recommendations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1957-1965; 168793 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Religion, 1965-1966; 168792 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Report to the Faculty, 1968-1969; 185368 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Report on Graduate Study in the Arts and Sciences at University Heights, 1966; 185369 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reserve Officers Training Program, 1968; 168791 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) Proposals, 1968-1969; 185370 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Russian Area Studies, 1965; 168790 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Scholastic Standing Committee, 1968; 185371 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Scholastic Standing Reform, 1969; 185372 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Science Requirement, 1961-1966; 168789 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Social Science Integration, 1962; 168788 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Spain, New York University in, 1960-1966; 168787 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Speech, 1962-1965; 168786 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Educational Policy Committee: State Proficiency Exams, 1957-1969; 185373 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Statistics Major, 1958; 168785 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Student Participation, 1969; 185374 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Student Petition on Tenure, 1969 March; 185375 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Superior Student Privileges, 1962-1963; 168784 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Terminations, Program of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963-1966; 168783 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Educational Polciy Committee: Testing: Advanced, 1961; 168782 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Three Year M.A., 1960-1964; 168781 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Television, Motion Pictures and Radio, Department of, 1963-1965; 168780 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Tutorial Group, 1961; 168779 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee: University Scholars, 1965; 168778 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Educational Policy Committee: Upperclass Programs, 1957-1961; 168777 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Educational Policy Committee: World Literature Minor, 1968 October-November; 185376 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Subseries D: Administrative Subject Files, 168423
    - Afro-American Course Offerings, 1969; 168775 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225993 0
    - Alumni Association Seminars, 1979; 168774 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Alumni News, 1979; 168773 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Relations, 1979; 168772 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - American Council on Education, 1962-1968; 168771 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Applications to New York University, 1973-1979; 168770 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Applied Economics, Center for, 1978; 168769 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Applied Mathematics Proposal, 1979; 168768 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Color Film on Greece, 1953-1956; 168767 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Archaelogical Institute of America: Committee on Films and Television, 1954-1971; 168766 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Greek Temple Film, 1958-1959; 168765 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Archaeological Institute of America: Visual Arts Committee, 1955-1971; 168764 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Articulation Programs, 1976; 168763 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Big Apple Volunteer Fair, 1977; 168762 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Chairmanships, Departmental, 1979; 168761 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - City University of New York, 1972; 168760 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Commencement: 1970, 168759 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Commencement: 1971, 168758 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Commencement: 1972, 168757 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Commencement: 1973, 168756 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Commencement: 1974, 168755 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Comparative Literature, 1963-1974; 168754 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225994 8
    - Comparative Literature: Undergraduate Major, 1979; 168753 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Confidential Task Force, 1972; 168752 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Continuing Education, School of, 1977; 168751 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970, 168750 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970: Cambodia, 168749 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Crisis Period: May 1970: Department Reports, 168748 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, Undergraduate, 1977-1978; 168747 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dean McKee, 1966-1971; 168746 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Deems Lecutre Committee, 1965-1968; 168745 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Degree Requirements, 1968; 168744 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Dr. W. Lewis Hyde, 1971; 168743 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Drama, 1965; 168742 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Empire State Program, 1972-1973; 168741 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Problems, 1970-1973; 168740 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1974-1975; 168739 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Faculty of Arts and Science, Minutes of the, 1974-1976; 168738 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Goals Conference, 1 of 6, 1973-1974; 168737 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225995 5
    - Goals Conference, 2 of 6, 1973-1974; 226306 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Goals Conference, 3 of 6, 1973-1974; 226307 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Goals Conference, 4 of 6, 1973-1974; 226308 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Goals Conference, 5 of 6, 1973-1974; 226309 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Goals Conference, 6 of 6, 1973-1974; 226310 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Harout's Experiment, 1969; 168736 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Humanities Program, 1971-1972; 168735 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Ibero-American Studies, 1965-1966; 168734 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - India, Seminar in, 1966-1968; 168733 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Institutional Services, 1968-1969; 168732 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225996 3
    - Inter-American Institute of Ecology, 1971; 168731 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - International Affairs Center, 1963-1965; 168730 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - International Development Research Center, 1969; 168729 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - International Education, Institute of, 1969-1970; 168728 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - International Research and Exchange Board, 1970-1972; 168727 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - International Student Center, 169158 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - International Studies Center, 1965-1971; 168726 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - International Studies Center: Policy Council, 1956-1968; 168725 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Internships, 1974; 168724 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Inventions and Patents, 1963; 168723 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Irish Studies, 1964-1973; 168722 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Israel, Summer Session in, 1968; 168721 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - J File, 1964-1967; 168720 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Japanese Studies, 1965-1966; 168719 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Junior Years, 169159 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Library Strike, 1970; 168718 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Linguistics Program, 1968-1972; 168717 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Lobbying, 1972-1973; 168716 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Lobbying, Higher Education, 1971; 168715 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Luce Scholars Program, 1973-1975; 168714 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Luso-Brazilian Studies, 1966; 168713 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - M File, 1963-1967; 168712 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Majors, Distribution at New York University, 1965-1975; 168711 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Management Development and Training, 1970; 168710 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - McGhee Concerts, 1955-1966; 168709 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - McKay Committee: Report, 1967-1974; 168708 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Medicine, School of, 1963-1973; 168707 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - M.D.-Ph.D., Joint Program at New York University, 1964; 168706 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda File, 1968-1973; 168705 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225997 1
    - Memoranda Issued by Dean of the Faculty, 1970; 168704 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Mental Health Center, 1968; 168703 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 169160 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Middle States Association, 1964-1973; 168702 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Mid-Term Grades, 1965-1968; 168701 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Minority Group Programs, 1968; 168700 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Model Programs, 1974; 168699 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Modern Language Association, 1964-1969; 168698 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - N File, 1963-1968; 168697 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People: The Committee of 100, 1975; 168696 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1965-1966; 168695 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Teacher's Agencies, 1975; 168694 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1964; 168693 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - National Defense Authorization, 1966-1970; 168692 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Applications, 1974; 168691 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Newsletters, 1975-1976; 168690 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - National Institute of Education, 1973; 168689 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - National Institute of Health, 1962-1975; 168688 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1973; 168687 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - National League for Nursing, 1966; 168686 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - National Research Council, 1967; 168685 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - New York State Correspondence, 1967-1975; 168684 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - New York State Education Department: Awarding Credit for Same Course in Different Degree Programs, 1971; 168683 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - New York State Education Department: Foreign Area Materials Center, 1971-1972; 168682 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - New York State Education Department: Programs, 1969-1975; 168681 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - New York Times, Challenge from the, 1970; 168680 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - New York University Press, 1965-1976; 168679 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - New York University Press Policy Council, 1969; 168678 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Nobel Peace Prize, 1972; 168677 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Non-Credit Courses, 1970-1971; 168676 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Non-Graded Courses, 1972; 168675 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Placement Services, 1963-1975; 168674 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Popular Courses, 1974-1977; 168673 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Priorities in Higher Education Task Force, 1969-1970; 168672 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225998 9
    - Promotions Pending, 1977-1978; 168671 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Promotions, Recommendations for, 1970-1971; 168670 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Recruitment, Admissions, and Scholarship, Commission on, 1965-1967; 168669 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Sabbatical Leaves, Applications for, 1970-1971; 168668 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Security Incident Reports, 1978; 168667 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Senate Elected Areas, 169161 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Union, a Guide to Study in the, 1959-1960; 168666 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Spain, American Academy in, 1963-1967; 168665 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Square Journal Clippings, 1959-1965; 169162 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Student Conduct Memos, 1968-1970; 169163 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Student Participation, 169164 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Student Union, the New, 1966; 168664 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: Dinner, 1963; 168663 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: General File, 1963; 168662 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Washington Square College Fiftieth Anniversary: Lecture, undated; 168661 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Washington Square and University College Council, 1973-1976; 168660 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Alcoa Foundation, 1976; 168659 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04225999 7
    - Financial: Ann Petluck Poses Scholarship Fund, 1975; 168658 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Benjamin Salom Memorial Award for Biological Research, 1972-1974; 168657 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Biology and Psychology, Fund Raising for, 1971; 168656 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Budget Meetings, 1978; 168655 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Carnegie Corporation, 1974-1977; 168654 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Classics Department, Discretionary Fund of the, 1972-1973; 168653 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Clubs, Budgets for, 1977-1978; 168652 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Danforth Foundation, 1971-1972; 168651 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Delmore Schwartz Memorial Poetry Fund, 1966-1974; 168650 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Development: Campaign Meeting, 1969; 168649 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Development: General File, 1969-1970; 168648 (Box 23, Folder 12)